CR is a free open-source art application
CR是一个免费的开源ART应用程序
for Windows Mac Linux and even Android
适用于Windows、Mac、Linux甚至Android
in my opinion it's by far the best free
在我看来 这是迄今为止最好的免费
option out there and it's better than
在那里有选择 这比
most paid art apps as well although Crea
大多数付费艺术应用程序也是如此 尽管Crea
is 100% free it would be wise to donate
是100%免费的 捐赠是明智之举
to support the development if you want
如果你想的话支持发展
this software to be around for the long
这款软件将长期存在
term C's development team is very
Term C的开发团队非常
forward thinking and Innovative in many
在许多方面具有前瞻性和创新性
respects CA is raising the bar on what
尊重CA在什么方面提高了标准
can be done to advance digital art
可以推动数字艺术的发展
software while it's much more technical
软件 而它更多的是技术
than some of the other artart apps out
比其他一些Artart应用程序更好
there it can be customized to be more
在那里 它可以定制为更多
userfriendly Crea is a Powerhouse of
用户友好的Crea是
creative tools you can make drawings and
创造性的工具 您可以绘制图纸和
paintings create Vector art anime and
绘画创造了向量艺术动漫和
much more there's a lot Crea can do and
更重要的是 Crea可以做很多事情
new features are added regularly in this
此版本中定期添加新功能
course we'll just focus on getting
当然 我们只会专注于
started with CA using the tools and
从CA开始 使用工具和
features I feel are the most essential
我觉得这些功能是最重要的
for making art let's begin when you
为了创造艺术 让我们从你开始
first launch CR you will be greeted by a
首次发布CR时 您将看到一个
new document dialogue let's just choose
新文档对话让我们选择
a3300 from the list of preset sizes so
A3300从预置尺寸列表中选择
we can move on to some initial setup the
我们可以继续进行一些初始设置
default layout is difficult to use
默认布局很难使用
because it's not well organized for art
因为它的艺术组织不是很好
and it conceals a lot of useful features
而且它隐藏了许多有用的特征
so before we do anything else we'll need
所以在我们做任何其他事情之前 我们需要
to create a better layout to make this
为了创建更好的布局来实现这一点
quick and easy I have provided a layout
我提供了一个快速而简单的布局
file you can import if you have the paid
您可以导入的文件 如果您有支付
version of this lesson you'll need to
本课的版本 您将需要
follow the installation instructions
按照安装说明进行操作
provided with the lesson if you're going
如果你要去的话就带上这节课
to set up the layout self everything you
要自行设置布局 请执行以下操作
see here can be found under settings
查看此处可在设置下找到
Dockers you may need to resize these
码头工人 您可能需要调整这些尺寸
panels to fit your display if it's
适合您的显示器的面板 如果它是
larger or smaller than mine the next
下一次比我的更大或更小
most important thing to set up is your
要设置的最重要的是您的
drawing tablet you can use crto with a
绘图板 您可以使用crto和
mouse but you'll have a more natural
但你会有一个更自然的老鼠
experience using a tablet with pressure
带着压力使用平板电脑的体验
sensitivity Press B or select the brush
敏感度按B键或选择画笔
tool and choose the basic five size
工具 并选择基本的五种尺寸
brush from the brush presets palette on
从笔刷预设调色板打开笔刷
the left select a gray color in the
左侧选择的是灰色
color selector on the right and try
右侧的颜色选择器 然后尝试
drawing on the canvas hopefully you'll
在画布上画画希望你能
be able to make a mark and your cursor
能够做一个记号和你的光标
aligns with your pen tip if so then try
与笔尖对齐如果是这样 请尝试
to use light and heavy pressure to vary
用轻压力和重压力来改变
the line width if that's all working
线条宽度 如果全部正常工作的话
then you can skip the next step if your
然后 如果您的
tablet isn't working properly go to
平板电脑无法正常工作 请转至
settings configure Crea and look on the
设置配置Crea并查看
left under tablet settings under tablet
位于Tablet下的Tablet设置下方
input choose the appropriate option you
输入选择您需要的适当选项
can choose between win tab which
可以在Win选项卡中选择
includes walkom and similar brands or or
包括Walkom和类似品牌或或
if you're using a Windows pen enabled
如果您使用的是启用的Windows笔
device then you might want to set this
设备 则您可能想要设置此
to Windows 8/ Windows Inc restart cre
到Windows 8/Windows Inc.重新启动CRE
for the changes to take effect if
在以下情况下 更改才会生效
neither of those settings get your
这两个设置都不会使您的
tablet to work in cre I have a
平板电脑可以在Cre中使用我有一台
troubleshooting video you can watch with
您可以观看的故障排除视频
more solutions you can find links to
您可以找到更多解决方案的链接
these reference videos in the written
这些参考视频以书面形式
transcript of this course I also
这门课的成绩单我也
recommend that you watch my free
推荐你免费看我的节目
reference video about how to draw on a
参考视频 介绍如何在
tablet because that will go in depth
平板电脑 因为这将深入到
into how to set up and use your
如何设置和使用您的
tablet now that our tablet is working
平板电脑现在我们的平板电脑正在工作
working we can create a new canvas I can
我们可以创造一个新的画布 我可以
click on the new button in the
单击中的新建按钮
properties bar in the top left or I can
属性栏在左上角 或者我可以
go to file new let's start by looking at
转到文件新让我们从查看开始
the canvas Dimensions this defines how
画布尺寸这定义了如何
large and what shape the canvas will be
画布的大小和形状
there are a few key settings to consider
有几个关键设置需要考虑
when creating a new canvas the width and
创建新画布时 宽度和
height determine the size of the canvas
高度决定画布的大小
and the resolution determines the
而该分辨率决定了
clarity and quality of the image
图像的清晰度和质量
currently the unit of measurement is set
目前已设置测量单位
to pixels but you can also Choose inches
到像素 但您也可以选择英寸
or something else if you're planning to
或者其他的东西 如果你打算
print your artwork inches is the most
打印你的作品英寸是最
common choice on the other hand if
另一方面 常见的选择是
you're creating artwork for the web
你在为网络创作艺术作品
pixels is the better option for now
像素是目前更好的选择
let's switch the unit of measurement to
让我们把测量单位换成
inches it's important to choose a canvas
选择一块画布很重要
size that matches standard print and
尺寸与标准印刷品和
frame sizes such as 4X 6 8x1 11x14 and
帧大小 如4X 6 8x1 11x14和
18x 24 this ensures that your artwork
18x24这样可以确保您的作品
fits the paper or canvas you're using
适合您正在使用的纸张或画布
for your print if the size of the image
对于您的打印 如果图像的大小
doesn't match your print size you'll
与您的打印大小不匹配 您将
either have to crop the artwork or add a
要么裁剪图稿 要么添加一个
border around it the new document window
新文档窗口的边框
offers several preset canvas sizes to
提供多个预设画布大小 以
choose from and you can also create
从中选择 您还可以创建
custom preset sizes to use in the future
将来使用的自定义预设大小
I've included some with the paid version
我已经在付费版本中包括了一些
of this course that you can install
你可以安装的这门课程
there are also Project Specific
也有特定于项目的
templates with preset sizes for
具有预设大小的模板
animation Comics and More I'll choose
动漫和更多我会选择
8x10 at 300 that's a standard 8x10 in
8x10,300英寸 这是标准的8x10英寸
print at a standard 300 PPI for the
以标准的300 ppi打印
resolution
决议
there's more to learn about resolution
关于解决方案 还有更多需要了解的
in digital art so be sure to check out
所以一定要去看看
my reference video on that topic in the
我关于这个主题的参考视频在
top right are the orientation buttons
右上角是方向按钮
you can use these to swap the width for
您可以使用它们将宽度交换为
the height and rotate the canvas
高度和旋转画布
orientation let's make this canvas wide
定位：让我们将画布变宽
on the bottom of the new artwork window
在新的插图窗口的底部
you can see the canvas dimensions in
您可以在中看到画布尺寸
pixels and preview the RAM usage under
像素 并在下预览内存使用情况
color you can select a color profile
颜色您可以选择颜色配置文件
since I am using a scentique display
因为我用的是场景式显示器
with a wide color gamut I can show more
有了宽广的色域 我可以展示更多
colors than srgb provides by choosing
颜色比sRGB通过选择
Adobe RGB I can unlock more colors to
Adobe RGB我可以解锁更多颜色
choose from when I paint the down side
从我画下边的时候选择
is that the artwork might not look as
艺术品可能看起来不像
vibrant on a different display that only
在不同的显示器上充满活力 只有
supports
支座
srgb if you click on content you'll get
SRGB如果您点击内容 您将获得
more options for your canvas there are
您的画布有更多选项
lots of options here but the only one I
这里有很多选择 但我唯一的选择
want to point out is the background
我想指出的是背景
color this is the bottommost layer and
颜色这是最下面的层
you may prefer it to be a light gray or
你可能更喜欢浅灰色或浅灰色
something other than a bright white you
除了亮白的你以外的其他东西
can change this in the layers panel as
可以在层面板中将其更改为
well I want mine to be a light gray
嗯 我想要浅灰色的
after that click on create to create
之后 单击创建以创建
that new canvas because we already had a
新画布 因为我们已经有了一张
canvas open you'll see two tabs at the
打开画布 您将看到两个选项卡在
top of the interface you can use these
在界面的顶部 您可以使用这些
tabs to switch between multiple open
用于在多个打开的标签之间切换的标签
documents I'll close the leftmost one
文档 我将关闭最左边的文档
since we don't need it let's use the
既然我们不需要它 让我们使用
save button in the properties bar to
按钮保存到属性栏中
save our demonstration canvas so we can
保存我们的演示画布 以便我们
reuse it I'll just call it blank canvas
再用一次 我就叫它空白画布
8x10 after that I'll close that document
8x10之后我将关闭该文档
doent so we can see the welcome screen
Dent 以便我们可以看到欢迎屏幕
when no documents are open the welcome
当没有文件打开时 欢迎
screen appears this gives you quick
屏幕出现 这将为您提供快速
access to your recent documents as well
还可以访问您最近的文档
as the new image and open buttons I'll
作为新图像和打开的按钮 我将
also mention that you can open saved
还可以提到 您可以打开保存的
artwork and access your list of recently
Artwork和访问您最近的列表
open projects from the file menu as well
也可以从文件菜单中打开项目
I created a document that is 10 in wide
我创建了一个10英寸宽的文档
by 8 in tall which now resides inside of
乘以8英寸高 现在驻留在
the cre interface you can imagine that
您可以想象到cre界面
crea's user interface is like your desk
CREA的用户界面就像你的办公桌
you have some of your tools on either
你的一些工具都在这两个上面
side just like you would if you were
就像你站在一边一样
working with traditional media you can
使用传统媒体 您可以
grab your paper and move it around your
抓起你的报纸 在你的
desk you can also rotate the angle of
您还可以旋转桌子的角度
your paper or canvas and because you
你的纸或画布 因为你
working digitally you can even zoom into
数字化工作 你甚至可以放大
your composition to look at it more
你的作文要看得更多
closely or you can zoom out to look at
近距离观察 也可以缩小查看
it from a distance if your tablet
从远处看 如果您的平板电脑
supports multi-touch that will make
支持多点触控 将使
navigation feel much more intuitive I'm
导航感觉更直观了我是
using a display tablet that supports
使用支持以下功能的显示平板电脑
touch so I can easily manipulate my
触摸 这样我就可以轻松地操纵我的
camera canvas with my fingers but you
相机画布与我的手指 但你
can do all of this navigation without a
可以在不使用
touchcreen as well we'll take a look at
触摸屏也一样 我们将看看
how to do that shortly just like your
如何在短期内做到这一点 就像你的
desk crea's user interface is able to be
Desk Crea的用户界面能够
customized if I don't like my color
如果我不喜欢我的颜色 可以定制
selector panel to be here I can simply
选择面板到这里 我可以简单地
drag it to the other side of my screen I
把它拖到我屏幕的另一边
can rearrange many of the items in the
可以重新排列中的许多项目
cre interface to suit my workflow I can
cre界面可以适合我的工作流程
even make the panels larger or smaller
甚至将面板制作得更大或更小
try to find the balance between the
尝试在
interface being easily visible to you
您可以轻松看到的界面
while conserving space for your canvas
同时为画布节省空间
if you've made any changes you can go to
如果您做出了任何更改 可以转到
the window menu and workspace new
窗口菜单和工作区新建
workspace to back up your layout this
工作空间来备份您的布局
way if something gets messed up you can
如果事情搞砸了 你可以
easily restore it if you find you are
如果您发现您是 可以轻松恢复它
constantly moving the panels by accident
不小心不断移动面板
you can lock them with the lock
你可以用锁锁住它们
icons now that we've created a canvas
图标现在我们已经创建了画布
let's learn how to navigate cre in the
让我们学习如何在中导航cre
next
下
lesson
教训